

# **CONTACT**

918 E. 22<sup>ND</sup> St. #202
 Minneapolis, MN 55404

+1 (612) 243-2726

garsho@yahoo.com

### **EDUCATION**

Web Development Certificate UFM Jan-July 2019

#### REFERENCE

Motohiro Nakajima, Ph.D.

Assistant Professor
Department of Family
Medicine and Bio behavioral
Health
University of Minnesota
(612) 625-0437

#### **Abdi Warsame**

Member of the Minneapolis City Council +1 (612) 991-4521

#### **VP of Operations**

Jean-Paul Bigirindavyi Boys & Girls Club 1 (612) 281-5735 jpbigirindavyi@bgc-tc.org

#### **LANGUAGE**

English
Swahili
Somali

# **ADAM UGAS**

Fullstack Web Developer

# **ABOUT ME**

People find me to be an upbeat, self-motivated, dedicated, outgoing, team player with excellent communication skills. For the past ten years I have worked in schools and with youth, and organizing large community events. Working with people is best job for me. I have a track record of community engagement and I created ways people to come to gather. I designed a Unity Gala event for the community to help raise funds for youth program that became successful. This year attendance was 400. Maintaining a consistent of 5th Annual this year. I can bring experience and willingness to learn in to your company.

# **KEY SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES**

- Outstanding communication, analytical and presentation skills.
- Knowledge in HTMLS5 CSS3 JavaScript JS AJAX Node Git
- Sharp, innovative, quick learner; proven ability to adapt quickly to a challenge.
- Community organizer work well with youth, and also parents.
- Worked with schools past ten years mostly in St. Paul
- Always want to improve and welling to learn from others

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Web Development Certificate University of Minnesota
- Microsoft Certified Professional Microsoft Certified Solutions Developer -Microsoft Specialist
- INTRANATIONAL BRAZIL "B" COACHING LICENSE
- USSF NATIONAL Y LICENSE
- USSF NATIONAL "D " COACHING LICENSE

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

University of Minnesota

June 2017 to present

Department of Family Medicine and Bio behavioral Health

## **Qualified Independent Contractor**

• Outreach • Research • Coordinated • Recruitment

Nicollet Middle School

End of 2017 School Year

# Youth mentor & Parent Consoling

- Specialized working youth develop relationship.
- One o one meetings with 8 grades to help improve
- Make calls and meet with the parents outside and inside the school

Wise Home Health Care Inc.

November 2015 to April 2016

# Medical Billing/ Database Billing

- Using catch database system
- Troubleshoot issues with electronic filings or address changes and update billing procedures as necessary, such as when an insurance company changes its billing policies
- Maintains payroll information through payroll database; directing the collection, calculation, and entering of data.

Higher Ground Academy St. Paul, MN

August 2007 to June 2013

Physical Education asst. /Coach